

{
    "0": {
    "prompt":"The Fool",
    "Answer":"Upright: innocence, new beginnings, free spirit \nReversed: recklessness, taken advantage of, inconsideration",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "1": {
    "prompt":"The Magician",
    "Answer":"Upright: willpower, desire, creation, manifestation \nReversed: trickery, illusions, out of touch",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "2": {
    "prompt":"The High Priestess",
    "Answer":"Upright: intuitive, unconscious, inner voice Reversed: lack of center, lost inner voice, repressed feelings",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "3": {
    "prompt":"The Empress",
    "Answer":"Upright: motherhood, fertility, nature Reversed: dependence, smothering, emptiness, nosiness",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "4": {
    "prompt":"The Emperor",
    "Answer":"Upright: authority, structure, control, fatherhood Reversed: tyranny, rigidity, coldness",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "5": {
    "prompt":"The Hierophant",
    "Answer":"Upright: tradition, conformity, morality, ethics Reversed: rebellion, subversiveness, new approaches",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "6": {
    "prompt":"The Lovers",
    "Answer":"Upright: partnerships, duality, union Reversed: loss of balance, one-sidedness, disharmony",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "7": {
    "prompt":"The Chariot",
    "Answer":"Upright: direction, control, willpower Reversed: lack of control, lack of direction, aggression",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "8": {
    "prompt":"Strength",
    "Answer":"Upright: inner strength, bravery, compassion, focus Reversed: self doubt, weakness, insecurity",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "9": {
    "prompt":"The Hermit",
    "Answer":"Upright: contemplation, search for truth, inner guidance Reversed: loneliness, isolation, lost your way",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "10": {
    "prompt":"Wheel of Fortune",
    "Answer":"Upright: change, cycles, inevitable fate Reversed: no control, clinging to control, bad luck",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "11": {
    "prompt":"Justice",
    "Answer":"Upright: cause and effect, clarity, truth Reversed: dishonesty, unaccountability, unfairness",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "12": {
    "prompt":"The Hanged Man",
    "Answer":"Upright: sacrifice, release, martyrdom Reversed: stalling, needless sacrifice, fear of sacrifice",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "13": {
    "prompt":"Death",
    "Answer":"Upright: end of cycle, beginnings, change, metamorphosis Reversed: fear of change, holding on, stagnation, decay",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "14": {
    "prompt":"Temperance",
    "Answer":"Upright: middle path, patience, finding meaning Reversed: extremes, excess, lack of balance",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "15": {
    "prompt":"The Devil",
    "Answer":"Upright: addiction, materialism, playfulness Reversed: freedom, release, restoring control",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "16": {
    "prompt":"The Tower",
    "Answer":"Upright: sudden upheaval, broken pride, disaster Reversed: disaster avoided, delayed disaster, fear of suffering",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "17": {
    "prompt":"The Star",
    "Answer":"Upright: hope, faith, rejuvenation Reversed: faithlessness, discouragement, insecurity",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "18": {
    "prompt":"The Moon",
    "Answer":"Upright: unconscious, illusions, intuition Reversed: confusion, fear, misinterpretation",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "19": {
    "prompt":"The Sun",
    "Answer":"Upright: joy, success, celebration, positivity Reversed: negativity, depression, sadness",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "20": {
    "prompt":"Judgment",
    "Answer":"Upright: reflection, reckoning, awakening Reversed: lack of self awareness, doubt, self loathing",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0},

    "21": {
    "prompt":"The World",
    "Answer":"Upright: fulfillment, harmony, completion Reversed: incompletion, no closure",
    "difficulty":3,
    "scheduledTime":0}
    

}